<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyCityTour</string>
    <string name="start_app_button_text">Explore My City!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_showcase">ShowcaseActivity</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Parks</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Fairs</string>
    <string name="tab_text_4">Movies</string>

    <string name="details_screen_label">Details</string>
    <string name="dummy_details_placeTitle">Place Title</string>
    <string name="dummy_details_placeAddress">Place Address</string>
    <string name="dummy_details_placeDescription">Place Description</string>

    <string name="place_title">Place Title</string>
    <string name="place_location">Place Location</string>

    <string name="placeTypeRest">restaurant</string>
    <string name="placeTypePark">park</string>
    <string name="placeTypeFare">fair</string>
    <string name="placeTypeMovie">movie</string>


    <string name="rest1Title">Mayfare Lagoon</string>
    <string name="rest1Address">8-B Jayadev Vihar</string>
    <string name="rest1Description">This is one of the BEST premium restaurants of Bhubaneswar. It serves Indian, chinese, continental and desi Odiya food as well.It\'s most preferable for Romantic dinner, family dinner, special occasion dinning and business meetings also.</string>

    <string name="rest2Title">Mainland China</string>
    <string name="rest2Address">Hotel Swosti, Jayadev Vihar</string>
    <string name="rest2Description">Mainland China is also a premium restaurant mostly famous for Chinese Food. The best part about this restaurant is, it\'s always calm and quit.This restaurant serves the best Chinese and Asian food in Bhubaneswar. As it\'s inside a resort, the pool-side dining has a different feeling.</string>

    <string name="rest3Title">Super Snax</string>
    <string name="rest3Address">Jayadev Vihar</string>
    <string name="rest3Description">Super Snax is also a premium restaurant mostly famous for evening snacks. This is one of the most favourite snack joint of rich people of the city.It serves the best \'chaat\'- which is a spicy Indian snack and it\'s filter coffee is also a must try.</string>

    <string name="rest4Title">Jungle View</string>
    <string name="rest4Address">Nandankanan Road, Chandaka</string>
    <string name="rest4Description">Jungle View is one of the most favourite restaurants of Bhubaneswar. It serves food of classic \'dhaba\' style and people just love them.It cooks chicken in bamboo and it\'s taste is to die for. The pricing is also pocket friendly, so attracts more customers.</string>

    <string name="rest5Title">The Chocolate House</string>
    <string name="rest5Address">Infocity Road, Patia</string>
    <string name="rest5Description">The Chocolate House is also one of the most popular snack joint of Bhubaneswar. This is famous for it\'s Muffins, Donuts and thick shakes.It\'s a very much pocket-friendly and mostly a students\' attraction. The ambiance is so good that it makes it an ideal place for afternoon chill.</string>


    <string name="park1Title">Biju Patnaik Park</string>
    <string name="park1Address">Unit-6, Bhubaneswar</string>
    <string name="park1Description">The Park was earlier known as Forest Park. Later, it was renamed to Biju Patnaik park after the name of one of the Ex-Chief Ministers of the state. The park is full of greenery and attraction for children</string>

    <string name="park2Title">Buddha Jayanti Park</string>
    <string name="park2Address">Lumbini Vihar, Neeladri Vihar</string>
    <string name="park2Description">Buddha Jayanti Park or simply Buddha Park is a famous park for couples in Bhubaneswar. It mostly gets populated by engineering college students. It\'s kinda also infamous as couples indulge in objectionable activities</string>

    <string name="park3Title">Ekamra Kanan</string>
    <string name="park3Address">Botanical Garden, Nayapalli</string>
    <string name="park3Description">This park is maintained by State Forest Department. This park is a small part of reserved forest range of the city. Being situated at the outskirt of the city, it\'s very peaceful and full of good vibes.</string>

    <string name="park4Title">Indira Gandhi Park</string>
    <string name="park4Address">Ashok Nagar</string>
    <string name="park4Description">This park is named after the first and only female Prime Minister of India, Mrs. Indira Gandhi. It\'s situated at the site where Mrs. Gandhi gave the last speech of her life on 30th October, 1984. After returning from that event she was shot by her bodyguards. So this part bears historical connection to it.</string>



    <string name="fair1Title">Tribal Fareground</string>
    <string name="fair1Address">Unit-1, Bapuji Nagar</string>
    <string name="fair1Description">This is a fare ground where Tribal fare is organised. In this fare people from tribal clan of the state come in a large number and showcase their culture, traditions and art.</string>

    <string name="fair2Title">Janata Maidan</string>
    <string name="fair2Address">XIMB Square, Jaydev Vihar</string>
    <string name="fair2Description">This is one of the most famous event places of the city. Most of the famous fairs, events, concerts as well as protests are done here. Most famous of the fairs is Art and Craft fare, in which people from all over the country come to showcase their hand made stuffs. </string>

    <string name="fair3Title">Exhibition Ground</string>
    <string name="fair3Address">Madhusudan Marg, Unit-9</string>
    <string name="fair3Description">This is the places where exhibitions are organizes. Auto fare, Science Exhibition and Handloom fare are some of the fairs organized here.</string>

    <string name="fair4Title">Walking Book Fair</string>
    <string name="fair4Address">Housing Board Colony, Khandagiri</string>
    <string name="fair4Description">This is a Book fare where you can find most of the famous old books that you can\'t find in book stores. This is a favourite destinations for book lovers of the city.</string>



    <string name="movie1Title">Maharaja Talkies</string>
    <string name="movie1Address">Bhoi Nagar, Acharya Vihar</string>
    <string name="movie1Description">This is one of the favourite movie theaters in the city. It\'s equipped with all modern equipments and offers all modern services. It\'s also the most pocket friendly theater.</string>

    <string name="movie2Title">Keshari Talkies</string>
    <string name="movie2Address">Unit-3, Kharabela Nagar</string>
    <string name="movie2Description">This hall is situated near the Vidhan Sabha of the state. This is a small theater mostly prefered by families. </string>

    <string name="movie3Title">Stutee Talkies</string>
    <string name="movie3Address">Unit-3, Kharabela Nagar</string>
    <string name="movie3Description">This is one of the oldest theaters of the city that is still functioning. The speciality of this theater is that, it shows regional cinemas.</string>

    <string name="movie4Title">Ravi Talkies</string>
    <string name="movie4Address">Lewis Road</string>
    <string name="movie4Description">This is also one of the oldest cinema halls. This hall only shows regional movies. </string>

    <string name="movie5Title">INOX</string>
    <string name="movie5Address">Unit-2, Shaheed Nagar</string>
    <string name="movie5Description">This is one of the three multiplexes of the city. It shows Bollywood, Hollywood and Regional movies as well. </string>
</resources>
